What? What? You can't do it, Hee-chan!
What about here?
I don't know.
Oh, it looks good, but...
Wow...
That's scary.
Let's put it back a little.
Uh... uh... here?
Yes! You lose!
Heh heh heh.
I'm down.
No!
Music
Three more rules.
That's three more.
That's a lot.
Usually one.
Eleven more.
Until we fill the whole place up.
I'm gonna put it back.
It's so easy to do it all over again.
It's so easy to do, okay?
One time.
That's okay.
I'll try it anyway.
Okay, okay, okay.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'm on blow your mind
I don't mind you trip blow your mind
My pretty smile you make the world a semmetha' night
I'm on blow your mind
Hit me now It doesn't make any sense
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
It's up now It's up now
You and me so
It's a continuation.
Look at this, ladies and gentlemen.
I noticed that the stick is now on here.
Let's continue.
They're redoing it, I'm sure of it.
Let's move on.
Hey. - Hey.
Ta-da!
Oh, there's something in the middle.
Here.
It's got a little bit of a moan in it.
Why? Why?
It's got a baby soul.
Stop it, baby spirit.
Oh, one thing... it's great.
Why?
Why do you have to put it on so soon?
You'll get lost in there.
Ta-da! This is a quiz for heroes!
But you know what's important in this kind of thing?
The tempo.
It's good. It's good.
Isn't it good to shake it up?
Yes, it is.
This is it.
It's kind of shaky.
Yes, it is.
That's great.
Great, great, great, great, great, great.
And then this one here, L-shaped.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wait, that's nice.
It's so cute.
Oh, scary... not this way.
Scary.
Oh, shit, I got two!
Oh my God, I got two pictures!
Oh, my gosh! Here we go!
That's what I'm talking about!
Dan!
Oh!
That's a first!
But are you going to see this one on this one?
Okay, let's do this one first.
In reverse?
Let's put the weight on this side first.
Reverse it?
How does that feel?
Humanly.
Oh, my God! That's good!
It's a work of art.
What?
What is it?
This one, this one.
This one's a bit...
There's no time for this.
Oh!
What?
Is that me? Let's do it, let's do it.
Let's do it.
That's what I'm talking about.
People always get scared of me.
I'd like to try it.
But is there a way to do it?
Is there a way to use it?
I just thought of that.
Oh my God!
This looks like it's going to fall off.
Oh, my God.
It's so close, it's almost falling off.
Oh, that's it. Just the middle one.
I'll try it.
I'll give it a try.
I can go this way, and I'll remember.
I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it.
What the hell?
It's in my nature.
But...
Stability.
Say stability.
But... aren't you going to stay soon?
Is there anything more?
Finally.
This way.
Free-floating... whatever you like.
Which one do you like?
I think I'll go this way.
You're going to use that?
I'd like to put this one here.
That's good.
I said, "That's good.
I'm just trying to be nice.
Are you okay with that?
I'm, uh, marriage-oriented.
I think that's why I'm losing.
You're all probably looking at the back of my head.
I can't do it.
It's pretty, it's pretty weird.
Well, you know, because, you know, we've come this far.
You're on a roll. From the very beginning.
You said you could do it.
I'm going down! I can't do it!
I can't do it! I can't do it!
I'll never make it!
Yes, you lose!
I'm down!
What's wrong, what's wrong?
It's fine.
We didn't cut it or anything... uncut.
Amateurs.
Amateur.
He topped amateurs.
Not fun.
Yay, it's fun.
Funny, funny.
So that's my practice, so I'll start here.
I'll do it with remarks next time
I'm going to make something while being sandwiched between two people.
I'm scared.
I'm going to make a candy charm project...
What's that?
I can put out something involving candy charades.
I see.